favro.com 2017-05-17

# Privacy Policy – Favro Help Center

1\. INTRODUCTION

Maintaining your trust for Favro AB and our affiliates (“Favro”, “we”, “us”, “our”) and our services is our top priority. This document, the Favro Privacy Policy for Favro, explains to you how we process your personal information when you for example visit our homepage, try our software services and or ask us to help you through support requests. Personal information is information that can be traced back directly or indirectly to and identifies you as an individual such as your name, address, email, physical location, or phone number (“Personal Information”).

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and we reserve the right to do so. Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on our website so please revisit it periodically. If you continue to use our site and services, or provide us with Personal Information following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy, this shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If the changes are material, we may provide more prominent notice or seek your consent to the new policy.

If you have any concern about providing information to us or having such information used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy, you should not provide us with any Personal Information and you should not visit our website, or use our services.

By using our site and services, or in any other way providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our processing of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you are an international user, you agree that any dispute over privacy or this Privacy Policy will be governed by Swedish law.

2\. WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Favro AB is the data controller of the information monitored, collected, used, stored or otherwise processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may collect both Personal Information (as defined above) and Non-Personal Information (that is information, which is not Personal).

Non-Personal Information will be collected, used or stored only on an aggregate basis. This collective data, which is used for internal purposes, helps us improve your online experience and facilitate your use of our services. We do not connect this data to any Personal information collected from you.

If we have collected information, which consists of both Personal and Non-Personal (“Combined Information”), we will treat the Combined Information as Personal Information.  
Personal Information will be requested when you engage in the following activities:

• When you subscribe to Favro

When you subscribe to Favro we will collect personal information about you, e.g. your name, title, email and physical location, and typically also your credit card information.

• When you visit our homepage

We gather information from your browser when you access our homepage in order to measure number of visitors and from where you are accessing the homepage, including your IP address. You can read more about cookies later in this document.

• When you request our help

Personal information may be stored in our internal systems when a request is sent to support and/or requests are sent for training and demos. The information provided during such communication would be name and email address; however additional information could be requested depending on the type of support needed.

• When you send us data to troubleshoot an issue

Sometimes a request to our support results in that we may ask you for a crash dump, a copy of your database or other information that might be sensitive for various reasons and that may include Personal Information. This information may also be submitted to us through a dialog that appears if you encounter a crash. This information will solely be used for troubleshooting and we will delete the information after we are done with the troubleshooting.

• Other Submissions

If you participate in a survey, contest, promotion, events, communicate with us via social media, post a comment to one of our blog posts or otherwise communicate with us where Personal Information is included we may collect this. For example information you include if you post an issue to our Twitter account about an issue you are experiencing. Note that if this information is not posted in a secure area, including Personal Information, may be visible to the public.

3\. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The main purpose of processing your Personal Information is to provide you with information, products, and/or services that you request from us or to carry out our obligations arising from any agreements entered into between us.

• We use the data to communicate with you through email and other means available including telephone. Examples of these messages include: (1) trial period messages – when you are on a trial period we will follow up on what you think about our services; (2) service messages – these will cover service availability, security, updates, and other issues about the usage of our services; (3) promotional messages – these include for example meeting requests, news and other information we believe may be of interest to you. You can at any time opt out of promotional messages by replying to the person who sent you the message.

• We may monitor, use and store the Personal Information you provide to us to improve and develop our products and services and improve your user experience, for customizing content of messages, our website and other means of communicating with you.

• Customer specific Personal Information is occasionally given to us to resolve and troubleshoot issues customers may be experiencing. If such data is provided, you grant Favro the right to access such data for the purpose of identifying and resolve the issue within your organization. Upon request, we can provide a confidentiality agreement as well as providing safe methods to transfer data.

• We may also use Personal Information for preventing misuse of the software, and to keep our service secure and to prevent abuse or fraud.

3.1. SHARING WITH THIRD PARTIES  
We do not rent, share or sell Personal Information about you to a third party if you do not agree to this, unless it is reasonably necessary in order to: (1) comply with a legal requirement or process, including, but not limited to, civil and criminal subpoenas, court orders or other disclosures in accordance with mandatory law; (2) enforce this Privacy Policy or any agreement you and Favro have entered into; (3) respond to claims of a violation of the rights of third parties; (4) respond to customer service inquiries; (5) protect the rights, property, or safety of Favro, our customers, or the public; (6) facilitate the merger or sale of any of our business or assets, in which case we may disclose your Personal Information to the prospective buyer of such business or asset; (7) work with trusted partners, agents and service providers who work on behalf of or with Favro under confidentiality agreements (see 3.2 below). We may further share your information to others within your organization that have evaluated or purchased our services. We may also share your personal information if you have granted us the permission to do so.  
We may share aggregated and non-personally identifiable information with our partners or others for business or research purposes.  
Favro, in our capacity as the data controller, will at all times remain responsible for your Personal Information being processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

3.2. OUR PARTNERS  
We collaborate with and allow third parties to offer services and functionalities in conjunction with Favro. We may share billing information with our service providers for the purposes of processing invoices, or share data with a security consultant to help us get better at preventing unauthorized access, or with an email vendor to send messages on our behalf. We may also share data with hosting providers, payment processors, marketing vendors, and other consultants who work on our behalf and under contractual promises of confidentiality. In particular, our Favro solution partners act as our extended sales force and a part of their commitment to us is to provide customers who purchase Favro through them with the best available service. Therefore, the solution partner through who you either (1) purchased our services or (2) came in contact with us through will receive your name and contact information. By purchasing or expressing interest in our services through a partner you allow us to share this information with the specific partner (and only that given third party).

3.3. WHERE WE PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
The information we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, various locations dependent on where our company’s systems are hosted. The data may be processed by employees who work for us or by one of our suppliers who may be situated in a country outside of EU/EES where the protection might be different. By submitting your personal data, and unless otherwise agreed in the specific case, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing.  
We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your Personal Information is treated securely and in accordance with applicable privacy laws and this Privacy Policy.

3.4 HOW LONG WE KEEP PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We maintain information about you for as long as we provide service to you, and longer for related business activities. After information is no longer necessary for our business purposes, we destroy the information unless there is an outstanding request or order to preserve the information, or otherwise is stipulated by law.

3.5. SECURITY  
We will take all reasonable technical and organization actions to protect your personal data from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access or disclosure, but we cannot guarantee the security of the data transmitted to us and any transmission is at your own risk.

3.6 DO NOT TRACK  
We do not respond to Do Not Track requests.

4\. COOKIES   
4.1. ABOUT COOKIES  
A cookie is a small text file that a website asks to place on your computer, mobile phone, or other device when you visit a website. A cookie can help the website provider to recognize your device, either for the duration of your visit (using a “session cookie”) or for repeat visits (using a “persistent cookie”), provide you with access to certain functions on the website and/or register your surf patterns. There are other technologies such as pixel tags, web bugs, web storage and other similar files and technologies that can do the same thing as cookies. The term “cookies” in this Privacy Policy refers to cookies and all such similar technologies.  
There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.

4.2. COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITE  
Favro uses the following cookies on this website, for the following purposes:

• Essential operational cookies: These cookies are necessary for Favro to operate the service you have requested. For example, they allow Favro to recognize you and then provide you with the service accordingly. These cookies are both persistent and session cookies.

• Analytics cookies: Favro use these cookies to analyze how the service is accessed, used or is performing. Favro use this information to maintain, operate and continually improve our service and ss, and to target our marketing of our services. These cookies are both persistent and session cookies.

• Functional cookies: Favro use these cookies to operate certain functions of the service in line with the choices you make. These cookies mean that when you continue to use or come back to the service, it is provided as you have previously requested, e.g. remembering your username and how you have customised the service. These cookies are both persistent and session cookies.

4.3. GOOGLE COOKIES  
Favro uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Use the following link to review their privacy policies and cookie opt-out procedures:  
http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html.

4.4. EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS  
Favro also uses cookies in ours email communications to personalize the email and track whether the mail has been opened or read and whether the recipient has used any website links contained in the email communication. This allows us to monitor and improve our email communications and website.

4.5. ONLINE TRACKING AND REFUSING COOKIES  
Most web browsers allow you to manage your cookie preferences and can be set to refuse cookies, or delete certain cookies. Generally you should also be able manage similar technologies by using your browser’s preferences. For example, in Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”.  
Please note that if you choose to block cookies, this may impair or prevent the functionality of the service.

If you don’t consent to our use of cookies you should either set your browser to refuse or delete cookies, or stop using our website.

If you have any questions or comments about Favro’s use of cookies, or if you would like to receive more specific information on what cookies we and our partners use and for what purpose, please contact privacy@favro.com.

5\. YOUR CHOICES  
You may at any time withdraw your consent for our use of your Personal Information, in whole or in part. You may exercise your right by contacting privacy@favro.com. However, Personal Information may still be retained by us for audit or archival purposes or as required by applicable laws.

You have the right to access your Personal Information processed by Favro. If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy or the information we process, please contact us at privacy@favro.com or write to us at Favro AB, Dragarbrunnsgatan 41A, SE-753 20 Uppsala, Sweden. We will provide you with information about the Personal Information we process about you free of charge once per calendar year (provided that you have asked for the information in a written request signed by you or that you have otherwise given proof of identity).

We will on our own initiative, or upon the request of you, rectify, delete, or complete any Personal Information in the register which we find is incorrect, unnecessary, inadequate, or outdated. You have the right to have incorrect details revised under certain circumstances. Please send such requests to privacy@favro.com specifying what you would like to modify.

We will respond and/or implement your preferences within 30 days of receiving your request. In order to provide any Personal Information to you, we will verify your identity and authenticate your access right before doing so.

Our site and services may contain links to and from the websites of third parties such as our partner network. If you follow the link to any of these websites, please note that these websites may have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for the websites or these policies.
